FRANKLINE KIPLANGAT

(+254) 724375662/ (+254)101003901 Nairobi, Kenya.

ID No: 32849179

D.O.B: 29TH JUNE 1996

GitHub: https://github.com/Frankline-Kiplangat **LinkedIn:** www.linkedin.com/frankline-kiplangat

Email: kipfrankline@gmail.com

Languages: English (fluent) and Kiswahili (fluent)

Personal Brand

I am a full-stack software developer who understands web application projects in depth, and I am capable at all aspects of development from project planning to creating documentation and support. I seek a company where I can use my experience and education to help the company meet and surpass its goals.

Technical Skills

Strong: HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, Python (Django), React, JavaScript, jQuery, MySQL.

Experienced: Node.js, Angular.js.

Personal Skills

- High performance computing.
- Strong organizational skills and attention to details.
- Strong communication skills, works well with teams.

Employment History

Data Entry Clerk (Remote) - Cloud Factory, Kenya.

October 2022 - To date

Duties and Responsibilities

• Invoice Processing.

Team Captain (Remote) - Cloud Factory, Kenya.

March 2021 – Sept 2022

Duties and Responsibilities.

- Guiding Data entry clerks.
- Writing Daily reports on the workflow.

Network Operator- Jumia Kenya

June 2019 – December 2019

Duties and Responsibilities

- Recording new stock as it comes in.
- Shipping products using Warehouse Management System; Preparing and completing

orders for delivery according to schedule.

• Nominated as the best employee of the month in November (2019).

Intern - ESRI Eastern Africa

June 2017 - Aug 2017

Duties and Responsibilities

- Creating maps and graphs, using Geographic Information System (GIS) software and data collection equipment.
- Analyzing and modelling relationships between geographic datasets.
- Gathering and reporting on GIS data and determining how sets are best utilized through GIS.

Education

Moringa School

April - Oct 2020

Certificate in Software Engineering- Full Stack Development

University of Nairobi

Sept 2014 - Dec 2018

Bachelor Science in Astrophysics.

• Second Class Degree (Lower Division).

Kabianga Boys High School

2010-2013

Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education (**B**+).

Interests & Hobbies

Networking, travelling, doing community work like planting trees and cleaning the environment.

References

1. Caroline Muthoni

Delivery Associate – Cloud Factory, Kenya

P.O BOX 30343-00100,

Nairobi, Kenya.

Mobile: +254713906417

Email: caroline.muthoni@es.cloudfactory.com

2. Mike Njihia

Logistics Manager- Jumia Kenya

P.O BOX 26106-00100,

Nairobi, Kenya.

Mobile: 0729146642

Email: mike.njihia@jumia.com